Dangerously cute and on the loose
Back to the Outback is a family, animation,
adventure film directed by Claire Knight.
Tired of being locked in a reptile house where humans gawk at them like they are monsters, a ragtag group of Australia’s
deadliest creatures plot an escape from their zoo to the Outback, a place where they’ll fit in without being judged.
Maddie (voice), played by Isla Fisher.
Pretty Boy (voice), played by Tim Minchin.
Chaz (voice), played by Eric Bana.
Frank (voice), played by Guy Pearce.
Zoe (voice), played by Miranda Tapsell.
Nigel (voice), played by Angus Imrie.
Back to the Outback is a 2021 animated family film that follows a group of misunderstood
Australian animals who escape from the zoo to find acceptance and freedom in the Outback.
It is directed by Clare Knight and Harry Cripps (in their feature directorial debuts), from
a screenplay written by Cripps, and a story by Cripps and Gregory Lessans.
The voice cast includes Isla Fisher, Tim Minchin, Eric Bana, Guy Pearce, Miranda Tapsell, Angus
Imrie, Keith Urban, and Jacki Weaver, and is distributed by Netflix Animation.
The film had a limited theatrical release on December 3, 2021, prior to streaming on Netflix
on December 10, to a generally positive reception from critics and audiences.
The tone is lighthearted.